Guide to the Salo W. Baron Papers, 1900-1980
Department of Special Collections
- Series 5. Manuscript Series, 86.5 linear (173 boxes)
  - SRHJ, vol. III, p. 1-100 (Box 256, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, vol. III, p. 101-200 (Box 256, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, vol. III, p. 201-300 (Box 256, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, vol. III, p. 301-400 (Box 256, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, vol. III, p. 401-500 (Box 256, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, vol. III, p. 501-572 (Box 256, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 11 (Box 256, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 16 (Box 256, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 16, p. 1-102 (Box 257, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 16, notes (Box 257, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 17 (Box 257, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 17, misc. (Box 257, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 18 (Box 257, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 18, notes, p. 111-151 (Box 257, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 18, notes, p. 153-237 (Box 257, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 19 (Box 257, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 19 (Box 257, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ, chapter 19 (Box 257, Folder 10)
  - SRHJ, chapter 19 (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, vol. IV, p. 1-100 (Box 258, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, vol. IV, p. 101-200 (Box 258, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, vol. IV, p. 201-300 (Box 258, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, vol. IV, p. 301-400 (Box 258, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, vol. IV, p. 401-500 (Box 258, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, vol. IV, p. 501-604 (Box 258, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 20 (Box 259, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 20, notes (Box 259, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 20 (Box 259, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 20, notes (Box 259, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 21 (Box 259, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 21 (Box 259, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 21 (Box 259, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 22, p. 514-614 (Box 260, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 22, notes (Box 260, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 22 (Box 260, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 22 (Box 260, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, vol. V, p. 1-100 (Box 260, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, vol. V, p. 101-200 (Box 260, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, vol. V, p. 201-300 (Box 260, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, vol. V, p. 301-400 (Box 260, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, vol. V, p. 401-500 (Box 260, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ, vol. V, p. 501-600 (Box 261, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, vol. V, p. 601-657 (Box 261, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 23 (Box 261, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 23 (Box 261, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 23, notes (Box 261, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 23, misc. notes (Box 261, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 24 (Box 261, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 24 (Box 261, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 24, misc. notes (Box 261, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ, chapter 25, p. 549-624 (Box 262, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 25, p. 805-900 (Box 262, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 25 (Box 262, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 25, p. 158-232 (Box 262, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 25, notes (Box 262, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 25, misc. (Box 262, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 26 (Box 262, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 26, notes (Box 262, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 26 (Box 263, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 26, notes (Box 263, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 26, misc. I (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 26, misc. II (Box 263, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 26, misc. III (Box 263, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, vol. VI, p. 1-100 (Box 264, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, vol. VI, p. 101-200 (Box 264, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, vol. VI, p. 201-300 (Box 264, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, vol. VI, p. 301-400 (Box 264, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, vol. VI, p. 401-500 (Box 264, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, vol. VI, p. 501-600 (Box 264, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, vol. VI, p. 601-700 (Box 264, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, vol. VI, p. 701-800 (Box 264, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, vol. VI, p. 801-850 (Box 264, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ, chapter 27 (Box 265, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 27, p. 1-100 (Box 265, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 27, p. 101-209 (Box 265, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 27, p. 1-72 (Box 265, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 27, p. 73-171 (Box 265, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 27, p. 190-245 (Box 265, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 27, p. 246-317 (Box 265, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 27, p. 284-351 (Box 265, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 27, p. 352-416 (Box 265, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ, chapter 27, notes (Box 265, Folder 10)
  - SRHJ, chapter 28 (Box 266, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 28, notes (Box 266, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 28, p. 210-310 (Box 266, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 28, p. 311-338 (Box 266, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 28, notes (Box 266, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 29 (Box 266, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 29, notes (Box 266, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 29 (Box 266, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 29, notes (Box 266, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ, chapter 29, notes (Box 266, Folder 10)
  - SRHJ, vol. VII, p. 1-100 (Box 267, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, vol. VII, p. 101-200 (Box 267, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, vol. VII, p. 201-300 (Box 267, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, vol. VII, p. 301-400 (Box 267, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, vol. VII, p. 401-500 (Box 267, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, vol. VII, p. 501-575 (Box 267, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 30 (Box 267, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 30, p. 465-540 (Box 267, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 30, p. 541- (Box 267, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ, chapter 31, p. 425-565 (Box 267, Folder 10)
  - SRHJ, chapter 31, p. 566- (Box 267, Folder 11)
  - SRHJ, chapter 23 (becomes 31) (Box 268, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 24 (becomes 32) (Box 268, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 32, p. 662-789 (Box 268, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 32, notes (Box 268, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 33 (was: 25) (Box 268, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 33 (was: 25), notes (Box 268, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 34 (Box 268, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 34 (Box 268, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 35, p. 981-1065 (Box 269, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 35, p. 1066-1107 (Box 269, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 35, notes (Box 269, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 35, 881-1000 (Box 269, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 35, p. 1001-1086 (Box 269, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, vol. VIII, p. 1-78 (Box 269, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, vol. VIII, p. 79-204 (Box 269, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, vol. VIII, p. 205-333 (Box 269, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, vol. VIII, p. 334-404 (Box 269, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ, vol. VIII, notes, p. 405-500 (Box 270, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, vol. VIII, notes, p. 501-600 (Box 270, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, vol. VIII, notes, p. 601-712 (Box 270, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 37 (Box 270, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 37 (Box 270, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 37 (Box 270, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 37, notes (Box 270, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 37, notes (Box 270, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 37, notes (Box 270, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ, chapter 37 (Box 271, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 37 (Box 271, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 37, notes (Box 271, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 38 (Box 271, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 38, notes (Box 271, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 38 (Box 271, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 38, notes (Box 271, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 38, notes (Box 271, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 38, notes (Box 272, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 38, notes (Box 272, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 39 (Box 272, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 39, notes (Box 272, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 39 (Box 272, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 39 (Box 272, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 39 (Box 272, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 39 (Box 272, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 39 (Box 272, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ, chapter 39?, misc. (Box 272, Folder 10)
  - SRHJ, vol. IX, p. 1-100 (Box 273, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, vol. IX, p. 101-200 (Box 273, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, vol. IX, p. 201-300 (Box 273, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, vol. IX, p. 301-400 (Box 273, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, vol. IX, p. 401-500 (Box 273, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, vol. IX, p. 501-600 (Box 273, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, vol. IX, p. 601-721 (Box 273, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 40 (was: 38), p. 1-100 (Box 274, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 40 (was: 38), p. 101-220 (Box 274, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 40 (was: 38), p. 182-300 (Box 274, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 40 (was: 38), p. 301-400 (Box 274, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 40 (was: 38), p. 401-499 (Box 274, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 40, notes (Box 274, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 40, part I (Box 274, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 40, part II (notes) (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 41 (Box 275, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 41, notes (Box 275, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 41, p. 304-370 (Box 275, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 41, notes (Box 275, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 41, p. 98-163 (Box 275, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 41, p. 164- (Box 275, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 42, p. 399-481 (Box 275, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 42, p. 482-560 (Box 275, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 42, p. 1-100 (Box 276, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 42, p. 101-163 (Box 276, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 42, p. 561-602 (Box 276, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 42, p. 769-900 (Box 276, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 42, p. 901-1038 (Box 276, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 42, p. 371-426 (Box 276, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 42, p. 427-45 (no order) (Box 276, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 42, rest (Box 276, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 42?, notes, p. 1-87 (Box 276, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ, chapter 42?, notes, p. 88-162 (Box 276, Folder 10)
  - SRHJ, chapter 43, p. 413-500 (Box 277, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 43, p. 501- (Box 277, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 43, notes (Box 277, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 43 (Box 277, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 43, notes (Box 277, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 43, p. 603-683 (Box 277, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 43, p. 684- (Box 277, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 43?, p. 1039-1159 (Box 277, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 43?, notes, p. 1-81 (Box 277, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ, chapter 43? (Box 277, Folder 10)
  - SRHJ, chapter 44 (becomes: 50) (Box 278, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 44 (becomes: 50), notes (Box 278, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 44 (becomes: 50), p. 1160-1260 (Box 279, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 44 (becomes: 50), p. 1261-1322 (Box 279, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 44 (becomes: 50), notes (Box 279, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 44 (Box 279, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 44, notes (Box 279, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 45, misc. (Box 279, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 45, p. 820-900 (Box 279, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 45, p. 901-977 (Box 279, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 45, notes (Box 279, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ, chapter 46 (Box 280, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 46, notes (Box 280, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 46, notes (Box 280, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 45 (Box 280, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 45, notes (Box 280, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 45 (Box 280, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 46 (becomes: 47) (Box 280, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 46 (becomes: 47), notes (Box 280, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 46 (becomes: 47) (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 46, p. 684-784 (Box 281, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 46, notes (Box 281, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 46, misc. (Box 281, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 47 (was: 41) (Box 281, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 47 (becomes: vol. XIV, chapters 49-52), p. 1612-1734 (Box 281, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 47 (becomes: vol. XIV), p. 1735-1863 (Box 281, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 47 (becomes: vol. XIV), p. 1076-1163a (Box 282, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 47 (becomes: vol. XIV), p. 1164-1236 (Box 282, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 47 (becomes: vol. XIV), p. 916-972 (Box 282, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 47 (becomes: vol. XIV), p. 973-1026 (Box 282, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 47 (becomes: vol. XIV), p. 1110-1258 (Box 282, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 47, p. 1-84 (Box 282, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 47, p. 1-115 (Box 282, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 47, p. 1-84 (Box 282, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 48, p. 1238-1298 (Box 283, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 48, p. 1027-1073 (Box 283, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 48, misc. (Box 283, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 48, p. 117-189 (Box 283, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chronological table of principal events and personalities to vols. I-VIII (Box 283, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 48?, misc. (Box 283, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 48, p. 1262-1321 (Box 283, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 48 (Box 283, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 48, notes (Box 283, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ, chapter 48 (Box 283, Folder 10)
  - SRHJ, chapter 48, notes (Box 283, Folder 11)
  - SRHJ, chapter 48?, notes (Box 283, Folder 12)
  - SRHJ, chapter 48? (Box 283, Folder 13)
  - SRHJ, chapter 48?, misc. (Box 283, Folder 14)
  - SRHJ, chapter 49 (Box 284, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 49, notes (Box 284, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 49 (Box 284, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, notes (Box 284, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 49, p. 186-286 (Box 284, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 49, notes (Box 284, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 50 (Box 284, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 50, notes (Box 284, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 50 (Box 285, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 50, notes (Box 285, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 50, p. 295-388 (Box 285, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 50, p. 389-452 (Box 285, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 50, notes (Box 285, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, vol. XI, p. 1-100 (Box 285, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, vol. XI, p. 101-200 (Box 285, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, vol. XI, p. 201-300 (Box 285, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, vol. XI, p. 301-400 (Box 286, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, vol. XI, p. 401-500 (Box 286, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, vol. XI, p. 501-600 (Box 286, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, vol. XI, p. 601-700 (Box 286, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, vol. XI, p. 701-784 (Box 286, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 51 (Box 286, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 51, notes (Box 286, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 51 (Box 286, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 51, notes (Box 286, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ, chapter 52 (Box 287, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 52, notes (Box 287, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 52, misc. (Box 287, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 52 (Box 287, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 52, notes (Box 287, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 52 (Box 287, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 52, notes (misc.) (Box 287, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 53 (Box 287, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 53, notes (Box 287, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ, chapter 53 (Box 287, Folder 10)
  - SRHJ, chapter 53, notes (Box 287, Folder 11)
  - SRHJ, chapter 53 (Box 288, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 53, notes (Box 288, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 54 (Box 288, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 54, notes (Box 288, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 54 (Box 288, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 54, notes (Box 288, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 54 (Box 288, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, vol. XII, p. 1-100 (Box 288, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, vol. XII, p. 101-200 (Box 288, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ, vol. XII, p. 201-300 (Box 288, Folder 10)
  - SRHJ, vol. XII, p. 301-400 (Box 289, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, vol. XII, p. 401-500 (Box 289, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, vol. XII, p. 501-600 (Box 289, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, vol. XII, p. 601-652 (Box 289, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, vol. XIII?, (chapter 42?), p. 769-869 (Box 289, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, vol. XIII?, (chapter 42?), p. 870-950 (Box 289, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, vol. XIII?, (chapter 42?), p. 951-1038 (Box 289, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, vol. XIII?, (chapter 42?), p. 1-72, notes (Box 289, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, vol. XIII?, (chapter 42?), p. 74-162, notes (Box 289, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ, vol. XIII, p. 1-100 (Box 290, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, vol. XIII, p. 101-200 (Box 290, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, vol. XIII, p. 201-300 (Box 290, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, vol. XIII, p. 301-400 (Box 290, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, vol. XIII, p. 401-500 (Box 290, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, vol. XIII, p. 501-600 (Box 290, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, vol. XIII, p. 601-700 (Box 290, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, vol. XIII, p. 701-800 (Box 290, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, vol. XIII, p. 801-900 (Box 290, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ, vol. XIII, p. 901-928 (Box 290, Folder 10)
  - SRHJ, chapter 55, misc. (Box 291, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 55, misc. (Box 291, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 55, misc. (Box 291, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 55, notes (Box 291, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 55, misc. (Box 291, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 55, misc. (Box 291, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 55, misc. (Box 291, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 56 (Box 291, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 56, notes (Box 291, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ, chapter 55 (Box 292, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 55, notes (Box 292, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 65, misc. (Box 292, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 56, misc. (Box 292, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 56, part I (Box 292, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 56, part II (Box 292, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 56, notes, part I (Box 292, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 56, notes, part II (Box 292, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 57 (Box 293, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 57, notes (Box 293, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 57, misc. (Box 293, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 57 (Box 293, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 57, notes (Box 293, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 57 (Box 293, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 58 (Box 293, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 58, notes (Box 293, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 58, misc. (Box 293, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ, chapter 58 (Box 294, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 58, notes (Box 294, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 58, p. 285-346 (Box 294, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 58, p. 347-421 (Box 294, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 58, notes, p. 1-51 (Box 294, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 58, notes, p. 52-104 (Box 294, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 59 (Box 294, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 59, notes, misc. (Box 294, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 59, misc. (Box 294, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ, chapter 59, p. 422-477 (Box 295, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 59, p. 478-516 (Box 295, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 59, notes, p. 481-516 (Box 295, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 59, notes, p. 517-564 (Box 295, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 59 (Box 295, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 56-59, misc. (Box 295, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 60, misc. (Box 295, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 60, misc. (Box 295, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 60 (Box 295, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ, chapter 60, notes (Box 295, Folder 10)
  - SRHJ, chapter 60 (Box 296, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 60, notes (Box 296, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 60, misc. (Box 296, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 60, misc. (Box 296, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 60, p. 115-184 (Box 296, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 60, p. 185-242 (Box 296, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 60, notes (Box 296, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 61 (Box 296, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 61, notes (Box 296, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ, chapter 61 (Box 296, Folder 10)
  - SRHJ, chapter 61, notes (Box 296, Folder 11)
  - SRHJ, chapter 61, misc. (Box 296, Folder 12)
  - SRHJ, chapter 61, misc. (Box 296, Folder 13)
  - SRHJ, chapter 62 (Box 297, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 62, notes (Box 297, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 62 (Box 297, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 62, notes (Box 297, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 61 (Box 297, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 62 (Box 297, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 62, notes (Box 297, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, vol. XIV, p. 1-100 (Box 298, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, vol. XIV, p. 101-200 (Box 298, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, vol. XIV, p. 201-300 (Box 298, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, vol. XIV, p. 301-400 (Box 298, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, vol. XIV, p. 401-500 (Box 298, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, vol. XIV, p. 501-600 (Box 298, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, vol. XIV, p. 601-700 (Box 298, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, vol. XIV, p. 701-767 (Box 298, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, vol. XV, p. 1-100 (Box 298, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ, vol. XV, p. 101-200 (Box 298, Folder 10)
  - SRHJ, vol. XV, p. 201-300 (Box 299, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, vol. XV, p. 301-400 (Box 299, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, vol. XV, p. 401-500 (Box 299, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, vol. XV, p. 501-600 (Box 299, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, vol. XV, p. 601-700 (Box 299, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, vol. XV, p. 701-800 (Box 299, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, vol. XV, p. 801-900 (Box 299, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, vol. XV, p. 901-1000 (Box 299, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, vol. XV, p. 1001-1054 (Box 299, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ, chapter 63 (Box 300, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 63 (Box 300, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 63 (Box 300, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 63, notes (Box 300, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 63, notes (Box 300, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 63, notes (Box 300, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 63 (Box 300, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 63 (Box 300, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 63, misc. (Box 300, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ, chapter 63 (Box 300, Folder 10)
  - SRHJ, chapter 63, notes (Box 300, Folder 11)
  - SRHJ, chapter 63, notes (Box 300, Folder 12)
  - SRHJ, chapter 64 (Box 301, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 64, notes (Box 301, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 64 (Box 301, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 64, notes (Box 301, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 64 (Box 301, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 64 (Box 301, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 64, notes (Box 301, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 64 (Box 301, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 64, notes (Box 301, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ, chapter 64, misc. (Box 301, Folder 10)
  - SRHJ, chapter 64, misc. notes (Box 301, Folder 11)
  - SRHJ, chapter 64, misc. (Box 301, Folder 12)
  - SRHJ, chapter 64 (Box 302, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 64 (Box 302, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 65 (Box 302, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 65, notes (Box 302, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 65 (Box 302, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 65, notes (Box 302, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 65, misc. (Box 302, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 65, part I (Box 303, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 65, part II (Box 303, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 65, notes (Box 303, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 65, misc. (Box 303, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 65, notes (Box 303, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 66 (Box 303, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 66, notes (Box 303, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 66 (Box 303, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 66, misc. (Box 303, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ, chapter 66, misc. notes (Box 303, Folder 10)
  - SRHJ, chapter 66, misc. (Box 303, Folder 11)
  - SRHJ, chapter 66, part I (Box 304, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 66, part II (Box 304, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 66, notes, part I (Box 304, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 66, notes, part II (Box 304, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 66 (Box 304, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 66, notes (Box 304, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 66, misc. (Box 304, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, vol. XVI, p. 1-148 (Box 305, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, vol. XVI, p. 149-272 (Box 305, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, vol. XVI, p. 273-400 (Box 305, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, vol. XVI, p. 401-500 (Box 305, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, vol. XVI, p. 501-600 (Box 305, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, vol. XVI, p. 601-700 (Box 305, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, vol. XVI, p. 701-800 (Box 305, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, vol. XVI, p. 801-876 (Box 305, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 67 (Box 306, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 67, notes (Box 306, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 67 (Box 306, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 67, notes (Box 306, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 67 (Box 306, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 67, notes (Box 306, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 67, misc. (Box 306, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 68 (Box 306, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 68, notes (Box 306, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ, chapter 68 (Box 307, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 68, notes (Box 307, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 68 (Box 307, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 68, misc. notes (Box 307, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 68, misc. (Box 307, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 69 (Box 307, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 69, notes (Box 307, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 69 (Box 308, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 69, notes (Box 308, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 69 (Box 308, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 69, notes (Box 308, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 69, notes (Box 308, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 69, misc. (Box 308, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 69, misc. (Box 308, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, chapter 69, misc. (Box 308, Folder 8)
  - SRHJ, chapter 69, misc. (Box 308, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ, chapter 70 (Box 309, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, chapter 70, notes (Box 309, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, chapter 70, notes (Box 309, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, chapter 70, misc. (Box 309, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, chapter 70, misc. (Box 309, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, chapter 70, misc. (Box 309, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, chapter 70, misc. (Box 309, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, vol. XVII, p. 1-100 (Box 310, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ, vol. XVII, p. 101-200 (Box 310, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ, vol. XVII, p. 201-300 (Box 310, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ, vol. XVII, p. 301-400 (Box 310, Folder 4)
  - SRHJ, vol. XVII, p. 401-500 (Box 310, Folder 5)
  - SRHJ, vol. XVII, p. 501-600 (Box 310, Folder 6)
  - SRHJ, vol. XVII, p. 601-700 (Box 310, Folder 7)
  - SRHJ, vol. XVII, p. 701-819 (Box 310, Folder 8)